A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1919-1952; Series 4; 20 Linear feet Boxes 5-24
  - Frishmuth, Harriet, 1928-1929 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Froelich, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Fromentin, Eugene, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Fromkes, Maurice, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Frost, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Fry, Roger, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Fry, Sherry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Fuchs, Emil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Fuhr, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Fujita, Jido, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Fuller, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Fulop, Karoly, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Fulton, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Funi, Achille, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Funk, J. Townsend, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Funk, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Fursman, Frederick F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Furse, C. W., 1925 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Gabo, Naum, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Gaertner, Lillian V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Gag, Wanda, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Gaillard, Ferdinand, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Gainsborough, Thomas, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Gaisan, A. H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Galanes, Demetrios, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Gallagher, Sears, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Gallanel, Bertha, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Gallatin, A. E., 1937 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - Galli, Alfredo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Galpin, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Gammell, Ives, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - Gamarekeli, Irakli, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Ganso, Emil, 1930-1941 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - Garber, Daniel, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Garceau, H. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Gardner, Fred, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - Gardner, Walter, 1934 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Garland, C. M., 1934 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Garland, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Garland, Sadie Ellis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Gargallo, Pablo, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Gaspard, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Gatthold, Florence W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Gattorno, Antonio, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Gaudier, Henri, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Gaug, Margaret Ann, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Gauguin, Paul, 1936-1941 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Gaulois, Alfrida Storm, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - Gaulois, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Gavarni, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Gavenchy, Frank J., 1930 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Gaylor, Wood, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Gearhart, May, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Gearhart, Frances H., 1928 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Gebhard, Edward, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Geddes, Norman Bel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Gee, Yun, 1950-1951 (Box 11, Folder 127)
  - Geerlings, Gerald K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 128)
  - Gehrmann, John S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 129)
  - Geissbuhler, Arnold, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 130)
  - Gellee, Claude, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Geller, Todros, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Gemito, V., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Genin, Lucien, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Genth, Lillian, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Gerard, Albert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Gerard, Baron François, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Gerard, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Gerbino, Rosario, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Gericault, Theodore, 1937-1941 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Geritz, Franz, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Gerome, Jean Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Gershwin, George, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Gerung, Matthias, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Gettelson, Marion, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Giba, Peter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Gibbs, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Gibson, Charles Dana, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Gidwitz, Rose, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Gieberich, O., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Giesbert, Edmund, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Gilbert, Murvin W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Gilbertson, Boris, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Gilbertson, Warren, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Gilchrist, Emma S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Giles, Howard, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Gill, Colin, 1928-1930 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Gill, Eric, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Gill, Sue May, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Gillespie, Abraham Lincoln, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Gillray, James, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - Gindertael, Roger van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Gino, Frank, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Giorgione, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Giotto, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Giovanni, P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Girolamo da Santa Croce, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Giroush, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Givianni, Matteodi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 169)
  - Giza, Stanley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 170)
  - Glackens, William J., 1929-1940 (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Glaman, Eugenie F., 1935-1936 (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Gleizes, Albert Leon, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Glicenstein, Enrico, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Glinsky, Vincent, circa 1888-1959 (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Goerg, Edouard, 1930-1931 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Goethe, Joseph, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Goff, Sudduth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Goldberg, Erich, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Goldschlager, Belle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Goldthwaite, Anne, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Golsberg, Daniel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Goltzius, Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Gonzales, Boyer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Gonzales, Boyer, Jr., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Gonzales, Eva, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Gonzalez, Xavier, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Goodall, Margaret, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Goodwin, Jean, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Goossens, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Bruce, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Gordon, John Watson, Sir, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Gordon, Leon, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Gordon, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Gordon, Watson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Gorky, Arkele, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Gorter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Goth, Marie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Gothard, William Harry, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Goto, Byron, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Goudiachvili, di Lado, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Goumas, Vasileos Theta, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Goya, Francisco, 1930-1936 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Goyen, J. van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Goyo, Hoshiguchi, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Gozzoli, Benozzo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Grabach, John R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Grada, Raffaele de, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Graff, Anton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Grafly, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Grafton, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Graham, Ralph Wadsworth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Gramatky, Hardie, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Grant, Frederic M., 1936 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Grant, Gordon, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Grant, J. Jeffrey, 1931-1937 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Grant, James A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Granville-Smith, W., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Grau-Sala, Emilio, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Graves, Abbott, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Graves, R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Gray, A. A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Gray, Florence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Gray, Mary, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Greacen, Edmund, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Greco, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Greenbaum, Dorothea S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Greenhill, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Greenman, Francis Cranmer, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Greenwood, John F., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Gregory, Angela, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Greiffenhagen, Maurice, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Grell, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Grehagen, Merton, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Griffen, Davenport, 1929-1931 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Griffith, Louis O., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Griffin, Nina K., 1932 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Griffin, Walter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Griggs, Frederick L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Grigoriev, Boris, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Grigware, Edward T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Grinnell, G. Victor, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Gris, Juan, 1935-1939 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Groll, Albert, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Gromaire, Marcel, 1928-1941 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Groom, Emily, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Gropper, William, 1938-1941 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Gros, Baron, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Gross, Chaim, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Gross, Earl C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Gross, Oskar, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Grossenbach, Marguerite M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Grossman, Edwin Booth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Grosso, Alfonso, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Grosvenor, Thelma C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Grosz, George, 1932-1939 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Groth, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Grotheurath, Ruth, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Grover, Jeanne, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Grover, Oliver Dennett, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Grubb, Eunice, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Grumieaux, Emile, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Grun, Hans Baldung, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Grunewald, Isaak, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Grunewald, Matthais, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Gruppe, Charles P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Gruppe, Karl H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Grust, F. G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Gualtiere, Joseph, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Guercino, Giovanni Francesco Barbiere, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Guggenbuhl, Walter, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Guilbeau, Honore, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Gundlach, M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Gunnarson, Helmer W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Gurrie, M., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Gussow, Bernar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Guston, Philip, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Guttero, Alfredo, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Guttman, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Guy, Vivian, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Guys, Constantin, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Gyberson, Indiana, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Haag, Charles H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Habermann, Hugo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Haberstettler, H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Hackett, Malcolm, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Haelst, Barthalomeus van der, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Haffner, Jean Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Hagerup, N., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Hale, Gardner, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Hale, Lillian Westcott, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Halicka, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Hall, Arthur W., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Hall, F. G., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Hall, Norma B., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Hall, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Hallberg, Charles E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Gallberg, E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Haller, Herman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Hallo, Quint, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Hallsthammer, Carl, 1927-1940 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Hallowell, Robert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Halmstrom, Henry, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Halow, Esau J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Halpert, Samuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Hals, Frans, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Hals, Nicolaus, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Halverson, J. Jensik, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Hamilton, Hugh Douglas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Hamilton, W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Handforth, Thomas, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 138)
  - Hanlin, C. Searcy, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Hannell, V.M.S., 1933-1939 (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Hansen, Armin, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Hansen, Bertha J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Hansen, Ejnar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Hansen, Oscar J. W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Hanson, Oscar Rabe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Hantke, Henry R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Haberson, Georgina Brown, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Harding, Chester, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Hardy, Heywood, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Harkavy, Minna R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Hartow, George Henry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Harmes, Elmer Esmond, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Harmon, Edith Boynton, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Harmquist, Harry W., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Harper, F. R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Harpignies, Henri Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Harris, Lawrence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Harshe, Robert B., 1938 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Hart, George Overbury "Pop", 1926-1928 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Hartley, Marsden, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Hartman, Bertram, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Hartmann, Arthur, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Hartrath, Lucie, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - Hartrick, A. S., 1927 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Hartson, Walter C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Harunobu, Suzuki, circa 1888-1959 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Haseltine, Elisabeth, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Haseltine, Herbert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Hasin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hassam, Childe, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Haswell, Ernest Bruce, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Haugseth, A. J., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Havell, R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Haweis, Stephen, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Hawkins, G. Milner, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hawley, Margaret Foote, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hawthorne, Charles Webster, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hawthorne, Marion, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Haylis, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Hazelton, Mary D., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Healy, G.P.A., 1934-1935 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Heil, Charles E., 1929 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Heilman, Horace, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Heintzelman, Arthur William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Heinze, Adolph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Heise, Wilhelm, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Heitland, W. Emerton, 1927-1939 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Held, John, Jr., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Heldner, Knute, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Heliker, John Edward, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Hellebranth, Bertha de and Elena de, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Heller, Helen West, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Hemessen, Katharina van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Hemingway, Grace Hall, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hempel, Arno, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Henderson, Elsie, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Henderson, Philip L., 1937 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Henderson, William P., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Henghes, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Henka, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Henkora, Leo A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Henner, Jean Jacques, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Hennings, E. Martin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Henri, Robert, 1933-1940 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Henri-Martom, J. G., 1928 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Henricksen, Ralph C., 1931 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Henricksen, Rolf, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Henry, Paul, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Hentschel, William E., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Herbin, A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Hering, Harry, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Hermanjat, Abraham, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Hermann, Frank, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Hermant, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Hermes, Allen, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Hermes, Gertrude, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Herring, John F., Sr., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Herter, Albert, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Herve, Jules R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Hesselius, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Heuser, C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Heward, Prudence, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Hibbard, A. T., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Hibbard, Frederick C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Hickock, Conde Wilson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Hicks, Morley, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Hidalgo, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Higgins, Eugene, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Higgins, Victor, 1932 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Highmore, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Hiler, Hilaire, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Hill, George Snow, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Hillman, R. S., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Hiroshige, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Hirsch, Joseph, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Hirsch, Stefan, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Hirschmann, George, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Hise, Ray, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Hobbs, Jess, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Hobbs, Morris, Henry, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Hodler, Ferdinand, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Hoeckner, Carl, 1933-1937 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Hoerman, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Hofer, Karl, 1934-1939 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Hoff, Margo, 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Hoffler, Othmar, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Hoffman, Harry L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Hoffman, Irwin D., 1938 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Hoffman, Malvina, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Hoffmaster, Maud Miller, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Hoheberg, Marguerite, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Hogarth, William, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Hokusai, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Holbein, Hans, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Holland, Preston, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Holland, Raymond, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Hollar, Wenzel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Hollingsworth, Will, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Hollstammer, Carl, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Holsman, Elizabeth Tuttle, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Holsman, H. K., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Holzhauer, Emil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Homer, Winslow, 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Homer, Winslow and John La Farge, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Hondius, Gerrit, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Hondius, Hendrick, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Hone, Nathaniel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Honthorst, Gerard van, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Hoog, Bernard de, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Hooper, Warner, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Hopkins, James R., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Hopkinson, Charles, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Hopper, Daniel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Hopper, Edward, 1934-1940 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Hoppner, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Hornel, E. A., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Horter, Earl, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Hosford, Lindley H., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Houdon, Jean Antoine, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Howard, Cecil, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Howell, Felice Waldo, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Howells, Abby White, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Howland, Isabella, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Hoyer, T. A., 1936-1940 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Hoyt, Margaret, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Hoyton, Bouvrie, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Hubbell, Henry Salem, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Hudson, Thomas, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Huettl, Alois, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Hugo, Jean Victor, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Humbert, Frederic, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Humphreys, Malcolm, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Hunt, Will Harvey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Hunt, William Morris, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Huntington, Anna Hyatt, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Huntington, Margaret, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Huntley, Samantha, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Hurd, Peter, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Hutchins, Maude Phelps, 1935-1948 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Hudson, Charles W., 1933 (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - Hutson, Victoria Ebbels, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Hutty, Alfred, 1926-1935 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Hyde, Herman, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Iacovleff, Alexandre, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Iannelli, Alfonso, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Icart, Louis, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Ilyin, Gleb, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Indenbaum, Leon, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - Ingerle, Rudolph F., 1935-1951 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Ingres, J.A.D., 1941 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Inman, Henry, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - Inness, George, 1926-1936 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Innocent, C., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Ipsen, Ernest L., circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Irvine, Wilson, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Isabey, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Israels, Josef, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Iwata, Chujiro, circa 1888-1959 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Jacobson, Oscar B., circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Jackson, Everett Gee, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, John, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Jackson, Martin, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Jackson, Muriel, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Jacobsen, Norman, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Jacobson, Emanuel, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Jacobsson, Edward Gustave, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jacoby, Graziella, circa 1888-1959 (Box 14, Folder 9)